Aliya Jackson

123 Bridge Street, Boston, MA 12345 aLiyajackson@exarnpLe.com (123) 456-7890

A Head Football Coach with eight years of coaching experience, specializing in offensive strategy, game planning, talent scouting, and leadership. A proven track record of developing and mentoring student-athletes to achieve goals both on and off the field.

Education

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Sports Administration

Boston College, Boston, MA September 2010 - May 2014

Key Skills

- Coaching
- Offensive Play Calling
- Game Planning
- Program Management
- ♦ Leadership

Professional Experience

High School Football Coach

Belmont High. Boston, MA I May 2017 - Present

- Manage all aspects of football operations for the Belmont High athletic program, coordinate with assistant coaches to develop game plans, and identify strengths and weaknesses of players to increase offensive output from 18 PPG to 27 in 2017
- Create dynamic offensive strategies to maximize player skill sets during game days, resulting in records of 10-6,11-5, and 12-4 over three consecutive years
- Achieve recognition as the offensive coach of the year in 2020

High School Football Coach

Bunker Hill High School, Boston, MA | August 2014 - May 2017

- Served as the head football coach for a prestigious athletic program, managed the development of 35 varsity athletes each year, and led the development of new strength and conditioning programs to reduce risk of injury and improve endurance
- Improved points per game from 20 to 28 in 2015 by creating enhanced offensive strategies based on player strengths and defensive play calling